{
    "subject": "resource/Yarkon_River",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Israel",
    "human_readable": "The Yarkon River is located in Israel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8388791680335999,
            "question": "Where is the Yarkon River located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5839666724205017,
            "question": "Where would you find the Yarkon River?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.583219587802887,
            "question": "In what country can you find the Yarkon River?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5566314458847046,
            "question": "Can you name a river in Israel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45714613795280457,
            "question": "Is the Yarkon River a river or something else?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4497554302215576,
            "question": "Which country is home to the Yarkon River?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4150277078151703,
            "question": "Name a water body found in Israel."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22413355112075806,
            "question": "What geographical feature is described as being in Israel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1977812945842743,
            "question": "What geographical feature is associated with Israel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1365756243467331,
            "question": "What is the name of the river mentioned?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Yarkon River is located in Israel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7776_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What geographical feature is associated with Israel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7776_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What geographical feature is described as being in Israel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7776_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a water body found in Israel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7776_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7776_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the Yarkon River, including its location in central Israel and its flow into the Mediterranean Sea. This supports the triple that The Yarkon River is located in Israel."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple mentions that the Yarkon River is located in Israel, supporting this statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}